[Praise] hey everyone welcome to my channel I am Nitin Pal with you and you are watching insurance guru, friends
which are useful for you in daily life If there are friends, to watch similar videos,
you must subscribe to our channel and also do not forget to press the bell icon so that you can get the notification of our upcoming video
first on your mobile, then friends before we can see it on your computer screen.
Come on, I want to tell you something about today's video, so friends who have
a policy of United India Insurance or who do less with United India Insurance, today
's video is very important for them, so friends who have United There is a policy of Indian Insurance
and they want to know their customer ID, then they must also watch today's video, the video is also
helpful for them and those who work for United Indian Insurance, they have to create their customer's KYC details
or customers who Today's video is useful for those who have to update their KYC details by themselves
and who have an insurance policy which is United Indian Insurance policy
and they have bought this policy from the market, then they do not get the customer ID on their policy. If so
, many such comments came that when they wanted to update their policy on DigiLocker, they
needed their customer ID and they did not know their customer ID, so if you have the policy
number or your vehicle number as well. If you have, then you will be able to update your KYC from it and you will also be able to know what your customer ID will be on your United
India Insurance, so friends, if you are late, then
you will be directly sent to your computer screen where you will be able to update your KYC and if you If you want to know your
customer ID, then you will be able to know your customer ID too, so let's start friends, then friends,
first of all, open the browser you use on your computer and open the
website in the address bar, when you open this website If you do, then you will have such an interface The press will appear
which you are seeing on your screen right now this is the home
page of United India Insurance many websites now here friends you are seeing an option of customer service you simply have to come here
and then here when it is down If we scroll down, we can see the second option Update Customer Care
Wise City Details Mobile Number Email ID Aadhaar Card or PAN Number Friends Here the customer can
also update his KYC by himself and those who are agents of United Indian Insurance Want to update customer
's details, want to update KYC, then they can also update customer's KYC from here,
so friends, if someone wants to update his GST number or an agent wants to
update his customer's GST, then United The agent portal of India Insurance
can update the GST number by modifying the customer ID. GST end number
will not be updated from this website, so friends, you see, when we update the simple KYC, then we have to click on it
. clicking on If taken, then the site will be diverted, a new window will open in front
of you, here you are seeing two options of policy number or vehicle number, if you have a policy number
, then enter the policy number, if you do not have a policy number You select the
vehicle number here, then after selecting the friends vehicle number, here you are simply filling the vehicle number, after filling the
vehicle number, you have to enter the capture here, after entering the captcha simply
If you go to the search option, then friends, after taking a little processing, the
detail story of which customer is registered against this vehicle will start, then friends here PAN number
and Aadhaar card, we can update anyone's phone If you want to change the number, you can
modify the email ID, we can do all these things from here and those who are customers of Policy Bazaar who
do not know their customer ID or anyone else should know their customer ID. So the first
option that we see is the Customer ID. If it belongs to Mr. So simply this is the customer id from here
we can note it down so friends now we have to update it and modify it then
go to edit option here and we will have a new one Pop will open here we see
first mobile number is visible if mobile number is correct then ok if not then update it
For this click on this and fill the new number here and if you want to connect the email then email
it here and then there is the option of Aadhaar card then there is the option of PAN card then friends all these
things are given to us here. If you want to do it, see now I am not updating the phone number, the phone number is fine, the
email is fine, the customer's income, Aadhaar number and PAN card will be filled, and then see friends, OTP will go to this number
, that OTP will go here to fill us. After all these details will be confirmed
, then first of all we are writing the Aadhaar number here, see friends, we have filled the Aadhaar number,
after that we are filling the PAN number of the customer here, after filling the PAN number Here we have to click on the option of Generate
OTP, so see, I am scrolling down, here
we have clicked on the option of Generate OTP, now it will take a little processing and
after processing, this registered mobile of the customer The number was on it, that OTP will go, now we
have to fill that OTP here and confirm it. If you want to send me then OTP has been sent to the friends customer care register number
and see friends, here we are getting the option to fill OTP, if OTP is not sent at once,
then we also have the option of OTP here. Friends, if the OTP has been received, then we have
to fill it here and if it has not come, then we have to respond from here, so friends, now I have received the
OTP on the customer's mobile, and I will fill it here, so friends, I have filled the OTP here. Have done and after
that I will do ok here, friends, when we will do ok and your OTP
will be valid, then see friends, a message has been sent to you on this pop up, Dear Customer, Congratulations, you
have successfully submitted your request for PAN Aadhaar. Update d se will be updated in your policy and you
will get d confirmation shortly so friends now we have to submit it from here when we will
submit it from here all the details which we had to modify or update This
whole process will be done if the customer updates his KYC details. If you want to do this, then you can do it like this
and if the agent has to update the details of his customer, then he can also do it through this medium, so
see friends, this whole process has been done and here the message has been sent, your details have been sent. Updated
successfully, now we close it from here, so friends, we have updated all the details of the customer,
again we will follow the same process to check, if we want to check,
we will write the vehicle number here. I am again putting the details of the same vehicle here and searching, so
when we search it, see friends, the details which we had just updated, have been updated here
or that means on the server of United India Insurance. The details have been updated against this vehicle,
the details of this vehicle have been updated, so friends, in the same way now, if this customer wants to buy a policy in future, then
he can mention this customer ID and if you have an agent and policy If you want to write and write
any policy for this customer, then you can enter this customer ID. This is the process
of modifying and updating KYC video in which I told you that if you
have to update your KYC by yourself then how can you update your KYC with United Indian Insurance
and if you have to update your KYC with your customer
If you do not know the ID, then how do you know
the Customer ID? Maybe that's all for today , I
will soon come in front of you with a new video, take care of yourself Jai Hind Jai Bharat